你已經把你的創業想法跟我說過無數次了
You've told me about your start-up idea over a 100 times now.
你著手去做了嗎？
Why don't you do something about it?
我怎樣才能融到錢，巴蒂？
How will I get the funding, Bhati?
不是每個人的運氣都像你那麼好
Everyone's luck isn't as good as your's.
你是什麼？
What are you?
什麼意思？
What do you mean
你是啤酒
You are a beer.
我現在就辭職
I will resign right now.
我的B計畫會被選中嗎？
My B-Plan is going to get selected?
你應該...-永不放棄
You should... -never quit
夥計們
Guys!!!
我放棄了
I quit!!!
開始創業吧
Now let's just begin with the start-up
我們三年前就開始討論這個問題了-納文，我們已經討論過這個問題了
We've only been talking about it since 3rd year. -Naveen we've already discussed this.
一年半之後，等你從巴西回來的時候
That by the time you come back from Brazil, after a
year and a half, Yogi will make some contacts here.
尤吉將在這裏建立一些關係
理解我一下，我現在不能辭職
Guys try to understand, I can't leave my job right now.
大家開始意識到我的潛力
People are realizing my potential.
我是公司的重要員工
I’m a valuable employee to the company.
聽我說
Listen to me.
一個新的矽穀正在這裏崛起
A new Silicon Valley is being upstaged at Hiranandani here!
而你卻還在用 Python 寫代碼
And you're still writing codes on Python.
每當這個國家的畢業生厭倦了朝九晚五的工作..
Whenever graduates of this country, get bored by their 9 to 5 jobs...
為了擺脫睏境，他們隻有三個選擇
So, to get out, they come up with only three options for themselves.
讀MBA
MBA
讀IAS
IAS
或者去創業
or Start-Up.
北京
Beijing.
我們準備開始在那裏擴張，比原計劃提前了6個月
We're beginning our expansion there, 6 months ahead of schedule.
一周內有個會議
Apointment within a week.
我們需要一個聰明人
We need someone smart over there...
像你一樣
Like you.
現在才是真正的選擇
Now is the real choice.
已經得到的一定比不確定的更好
One in hand is obviously better than one not-so-sure in the bush.
是納文讓我來這兒的
He's the one who requested me to come here.
他..
He...
不得不馬上離開
... had to leave urgently.
讓我用啤酒再給你們講一遍
Let me explain it to you, with beer today.
它不會燙傷你，隻會灑出來
It won't burn, even if it spills.
你回來了
You're back!!!
我就知道你會來的
I knew it, you'd come!
阿克希爾給我們坑了
Akhil gave us the wrong information!
我們的名字不在獲勝者名單上
Our name's not on the winner's list!
但是等等..
But wait...
現在我的薪水怎麼辦？
What about my salary now?
如果你不能用兩塊披薩餵飽你的團隊，說明團隊人太多了
媽媽! 我不想結婚
MOM! I don't want to get married!!!
我才27歲，還冇到結婚的年齡
I'm only 27. Not even old enough to get married!
不要叫我尚娜·貝塔
Don't "Shona beta" me!
媽媽... 媽媽，別對我撒謊，好嗎？
Mummy... Mummy, don't lie to me, OK?
你冇有得甲狀腺癌
You don't have any Thyroid cancer!
好的，等等... 我接到另一個電話
OK wait... I'm getting another call.
是的... 等等! 等等
Yeah... Wait! Wait!
餵？是阿爾蒂嗎？
Yeah Aarti?
實際上還冇有，我還在開會
Actually no. I'm still in a client meeting.
你在哪兒？
Where are you?
哦，你已經到了？
Oh, you've already reached?
在哪裏？
Where?
好的好的
OK. OK.
這麼說你已經到了？
You've just reached, then?
不不不..
No, no, no...
我的會議... 可以取消
My client meeting... can be cancelled!
是的，我在路上了
Yeah, I'm on my way!
我們走
Let's go.
我們隨便繞一圈再回來
We've to go around and then come back here!
快點
Come on!
開車啊
Come on already!
嗨
Hi!
對不起，我來晚了
Sorry, I got a little late.
希望我冇有讓你等太久
Hope I didn't keep you waiting for long!
不
No!
氣氛不錯
Nice ambience!
你點了什麼嗎？
Did you order anything?
兩杯卡佈奇諾
Akhilesh, 2 cappuccinos!
不... 我什麼都不想要
No... I don't want to have anything!
不不……我自己喝兩杯
No, no. Both are for me.
我現在喝一杯，另一杯等涼了再喝
I'll drink one now, and the other one later, once it gets cold.
在這點冰咖啡要額外收一百塊
These guys charge 100 bucks extra for cold coffee!
順便說一句
By the way...
你看起來..
You look...
和你的照片完全不同
Quite different from your pictures!
我知道
I know!
我不上相
I'm not photogenic!
我是說..
I mean...
我在現實生活中看起來還不錯
I look good in real life!
但是我的照片，照出來效果不是很好
But my pictures, don't come out that great!
你以前約過嗎？
You've met guys before... like this?
嗯
Yes!
兩三次吧
2-3 times
我也約過
Me too!
六次
6 times!!!
你知道..
You know...
自從我從印度管理學院畢業之後
Since I've completed my P.G. from IIM Indore?
我媽讓姑娘們排隊等著我去見她們
Mom's had girls lined up for me to meet!
我告訴她”媽媽..
I told her, "Mom...
我現在不能結婚
...I can't marry right now!...
我想探索這個世界……
...I want to explore the world...
和朋友一起旅行……
...Travel with friends...
... 潛水..
...Scuba dive...
滑翔"
...Sky dive"
我告訴你... 你也應該停止這種行為
I'm telling you... You too should stop with this marraige shabang!
婚姻根本毫無意義
Marriage doesn't even make sense
像我們這樣的年輕人應該玩得開心
Youngsters like us should have fun!
但我覺得我媽強迫我註冊賬號是好事
It's a good thing actually, that my mom forcefully made me a profie.
否則，我們就不會有今天的約會了
Or else, we wouldn't have been on this date!
等一下
Wait a minute!
你媽媽... 讓你..
Your mom... made your...
註冊約炮軟件？
Tinder profile?
約炮？
Tinder?
不，不，是 shaadi. com
No, no. Shaadi.com
你是..
You're..
嗨
Hi.
尼基塔？
Nikita?
尼基塔
Nikita.
尼基塔？
Nikita?
尼基塔
Nikita.
哦..
Oh...
哦，糟了……
Oh shit... shit!
抱歉抱歉
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
我有點懵逼
I got confused!
幸好他提前來了
It's a good thing he showed up early!
我們就要……
We were about to get...
我們就要結婚了
WE were about to get married!
索拉佈 · 曼達爾
Saurabh Mandal!
我是科技公司的市場主管
I'm a marketing head in Technity.
你是做什麼的？
And what do you do?
今天是星期四？
Today's Thursday?
是的
Yes.
星期四我..
On Thursdays I...
練腿
...do legs!
健身房
Gym!!!
不錯... 不錯
Nice... Nice
請坐! 你們聊
Please have a seat! Enjoy!
你們聊
Enjoy!
玩得開心
And have fun also.
索拉佈先生？
Mr. Saurabh?
阿蒂？
Aarti?
是這樣，阿蒂，我想在開始之前先澄清一些事情
Actually, Aarti. I wanted to clear something first, before we start.
索拉佈先生，我知道你想說什麼
Mr. Saurabh, I know what you want to say.
你以前有過女朋友，是嗎？
That you've had girlfriends before this, isn't it?
我知道
I know.
不是，不是這樣的
No, not really. That's not it.
你怎麼知道我喜歡卡佈奇諾？
How did you know that I like cappuccino?
阿蒂，聽著..
Aarti, look...
我一開始就不想來這裏
I didn't want to come here in the first place
我媽逼我來的
It's just that my mom wanted me to be here.
父母逼婚，你懂的
You know how parents pressurize you
你的..
Your...
你的小胡子和阿尼爾·卡普爾的一模一樣
Your moustache is just like Anil Kapoor's!
不，阿蒂..
No look, Aarti...
事實上，我不能跟你結婚
Actually, I can't go ahead with this marriage!
索拉佈先生，我理解你的不情願
Mr. Saurabh, I understand your reluctance!
你要多少糖
How much sugar?
一包
One.
跟我一樣
Just like me!
跟你說實話吧
Look, if I were to tell you the truth...
在這之前我也有過兩個男朋友
I too, had two boyfriends before this
而且我和他們也很親密
And I got intimate with them, as well!
但我們冇有做任何“骯髒”的事情
But we didn't do anything "dirty".
我隻會……
That I will do...
和我的丈夫做
...only with my husband.
畢竟，我是一個印度人
After all, I'm an Indian!
我怎麼能忘本呢
How can I forget my roots and culture
阿蒂，毫無疑問，你是個很好的女孩..
Aarti. No doubt, you're a very nice girl...
潘迪先生也是這麼說的
Panditji too, says the same
不，不，現在..
No, no. Now...
我..
Now, I...
索拉佈先生，我同意了
Mr. Saurabh, it's a yes for me.
隻是..
Just...
別像上一個家夥..
Like the last guy...
不要對我隱瞞任何事
Don't hide anything from me!
為什麼... 他隱瞞了什麼？
Why... What did the last one hide?
我和他的婚事已經確定了……
My marriage with him had been confirmed.
但就在訂婚前幾天..
But just a few days before the engagement...
我爸爸知道了
...dad got to know that...
他辭掉了一份穩定的工作，準備開始創業
...he was quitting a stable job to begin a start-up!
然後我們的婚事就此結束了
And the marriage got canned, then and there.
後來我就看到了你的資料
That's when I saw your profile and...
就算他要創業又怎樣
So what, if he was going to begin a start-up?
為什麼女孩要嫁給創業者？
Why would any girl marry a "start-up guy"?
現在這個時代... 如果公司做得不好..
Now... If the company doesn't do well...
我難道要放下家務出門工作嗎？
Will I have to leave my household chores and go do a job?
你說呢，索拉佈先生？
Tell me Mr. Saurabh?
實際上，阿蒂
Actually, Aarti...
這正是我想告訴你的..
This is exactly, what I wanted to tell you about...
從明天開始自己洗衣服
No laundry from tomorrow!
告別保潔阿姨
No maid from tomorrow!
告別牛奶
No milk from tomorrow!
連報紙都要告別
Even, no newspaper from tomorrow!
告別健身房會員
Gym membership will be cancelled!
出門坐地鐵
Metros will be used instead of the car!
節約用電
Electricity will be saved!
寬帶從8mbps 降低到1mbps
Internet speed will be reduced from 8mbps to 1mbps!
別啊，兄弟
No. No. No. No dude.
寬帶就別降了
Atleast let the net speed stay!
難道你不想要傑圖了嗎？
Do you not want Jeetu, then?
如果我們存的錢不夠，怎麼保證他的工資呢？
If we don't save enough, how will we ensure his salary?
好吧，讓我們把速度從8mbps 降低到4mbps
Alright then. Let's reduce the speed from 8mbps to 4mbps.
付費電視停掉
Table top-ups will be stopped!
外賣停掉
Ordering food from restaurants will be stopped!
絕對要停
Will be absolutely stopped!
實際上，任何奢侈消費都要停
Infact, all kinds of luxury expenditures will be absolutely stopped!
現在有多少了
What's the total?
三仟
Three thousand
七百
Seven hundred
二十五
Twenty-five.
再加上我的份額..
And adding my share to it...
七仟
Seven thousand
四百
Four hundred
五十
Fifty.
傑圖的工資是多少？
And how much is Jeetu's salary?
一個月
One lac
三萬七仟
Thirty seven thousand
五百
Five hundred.
好計劃
Superb plan!
我們可以存一年半的錢
We'll save for a year and a half...
支付一個月的薪水
...and shell out one month's salary!
“歐耶! ”
"Alright!"
曼達爾，你在幹什麼
Madal, what are you doing dude?
什麼？
What?
你在幹什麼？
What are you doing?
音樂
Music!
吵鬨的音樂
Loud music!
什麼都聽不見
Can't hear a thing!
你繼續幹吧
You carrry on!
“歐耶! ”
"Alright!"
我想說的是..
What I'm saying is...
我們再加50塊..
Let's add another 50 bucks to this...
找幾個實習生來寫代碼
And hire some intern to do the coding.
尤吉，實習生能替代傑圖嗎？
Yogi, an intern will replace Jeetu, now?
我們公司需要有工作經驗的人
We need people with some work experience in our compnay!
在高層工作過的人
People who've worked at some senior level!
能組建團隊的人
Someone who can build a team in the future...
能夠製定戰略的人
Someone who can strategize!
納文..
Naveen...
你找到我的那件 t 恤了嗎？
Did you find that t-shirt of mine?
什麼 t 恤？
What t-shirt?
‘ InfoCom’那個
The 'InfoCom' one.
我在那裏工作了四年
Where I'd an experience of 4 years?
作為高級顧問
As a Senior Consultant!
因為我組建了一個團隊..
Since I'd BUILT a team there...
他們把那件 t 恤送給了我
They'd gifted that t-shirt to me.
我不知道，我們現在很忙
I don't know dude. We're busy right now!
媽的
Shit!
現在我得想想該穿什麼了
Now, I'll have to strategize what to wear!
那我們該怎麼辦？
What do we do then?
夥計，我覺得我們卡在這了
Dude, I think we're getting a little impatient here!
我在想如果..
I was thinking, what if...
傑圖設法說服了桑亞
Jeetu manages to convince Soumya!
納文..
Naveen...
那是他的妻子
She's his wife!
她能跟他上床
She gives him sex!
你永遠不能說服一個能跟你上床的女人
You can never convince a woman who gives you sex!
相信我
Trust me.
這都是經驗之談
This is all coming from experience!
聽著，尤吉……
Look Yogi...
冇有傑圖，就冇有公司
Without Jeetu, we have no company.
納文..
Naveen...
我們現在冇有工作
We've no jobs.
不管有冇有傑圖，我們都得開一家公司
We have to start a company, with or without Jeetu.
尤吉……
Yogi...
你在幹什麼？
What are you doing?
你有冇有考慮好？
Did you think about it?
我昨天問了你什麼？
I'd asked you something, yesterday?
你問了什麼？
What'd you asked?
那個事……
That thing...
我能加入你們的創業嗎？
Can I be part of your start-up?
什麼？
WHAT?
為什麼？
WHY?
你說“為什麼”是什麼意思？
What do you mean by "Why?"?
你們都是工程師
You all are engineers!
你需要一個有MBA的人
You need an MBA!
如果冇有商業專長，你們如何經營一家公司？
How will you'll run a company without business expertise?
曼達爾，我還冇考慮好
Mandal, I'll let you know!
給我點時間
Give me some time.
這是一個非常重要的職業決定
It's a very important professional decision!
我會告訴你的，好嗎?-好的
I'll let you know, alright? -OK
那麼你會給我發郵件，還是口頭交流？
So will you send me a mail, or you'll communicate verbally?
我能在星期五之前接到電話嗎？
Should I expect a call by Friday?
我會..
I'll...
等星期五幹什麼? 真是個可愛的孩子
Why Friday? He's a sweet kid!
今天就讓我們來給你麵試吧
Let's do your G.D. and P.I. today itself!
明天揭曉結果
And the results tomorrow.
今天麵試？
Personal interview, today?
已經10點了，我什麼時候準備... ..
Iit's already 10. When will I prepare...
媽的，已經10點了？
Fuck, it's 10 already?
要死要死要死
I'm going to get killed!
10點怎麼了？
What if it's 10?
‘ Jhalak’隻在晚上10點出現
'Jhalak' comes up only at 10 in the night!
不行，尤吉! 我得去見史瑞雅，如果我遲到了，她會整死我的
No Yogi! I've to meet Shreya. If I get late, she'll screw me!
你不是已經告訴她我們的創業的事了嗎？
Haven't you told her already, about our start-up?
我都好幾天冇見她了
Where have I met her, since so many days?
曼達爾
MANDAL!
我的洗麵奶呢？
Where's my face-wash dude?
那個庫魯勒本草洗麵奶？
The 'Kurule' medical therapy one?
別用那個
Don't use that!
我用了之後它和我的四個粉刺結合成一個癤子
I used it and 4 of my pimples combined into a boil!
不是，我的洗麵奶
No dude. My face-wash!
你要去找洗麵奶嗎？還是我們應該在麵試前取消你的資格？
Will you get it, or should we disqualify you before the interview round, itself?
我正要去呢
I was just about to go!
聽著..
Dude, look...
有個程序員..
There's this coder...
他才大三
He's in the third year.
他是我一個朋友的叔叔的兒子
He's the son of the paternal uncle of a mutual friend!
他就像是我的家人
He's almost family!
我們帶上他吧，我嚮你保證，他會很棒的
Let's get him onboard. I assure you, he'll rock!
聽著，尤吉
Look, Yogi!
公司的一切都在於人
A comapny's all about the people in it.
你認為，任何一個大學生都可以取代傑圖
You think, any college guy can replace Jeetu...
如果我們這樣隨機招人，那為什麼我們不雇傭曼達爾呢？
If that's how randomly we want to hire people, why don't we hire Mandal as well?
對不起，打擾了你的重要會議
Sorry to disturb your important meeting!
但是我希望你能做出正確的決定
But I hope you take the right decision!
我也很看好傑圖
I also love Jeetu!
雖然已經過去三年了，我當年還是抄他的答題卡畢業的
Though 3 years late, I've passed by cheating from his answer sheet.
我當然希望他能加入
We definitely want him onboard.
但目前我們不能滿足他的工資，而且急需一個程序員
But till the time we do not ensure his salary, we need a coder.
我告訴你..
I'm telling you...
我們去見見這個家夥..
Let's go meet this guy...
然後就開始幹吧
And let's get the fucking thing started!
好吧
OK, alright.
現在我先去見史瑞雅
Let me meet Shreya for now.
然後，我們下午去見那個家夥，好嗎？
After that, let's go meet this guy, in the afternoon. OK?
我看起來怎麼樣？
How do I look?
還行
Fair!
好吧，借過，我去找史瑞雅，然後再聯係你
OK. You make a move, I'll go meet Shreya and then catch you!
走走走走
Go. Go. Go. Go.
餵？
Hello?
納文-嗨，史瑞雅
Naveen!!! - Hey Shreya!
你還冇有升級你的寬帶，對不對
You still haven't upgraded your internet, have you?
近來可好？
How are you?
你真是個守財奴，一輩子守財奴
You've always been and always will be a miser!
你能看見我嗎？
Can you see me?
等一下
Wait a second.
你能看見我？
You can see me?
我現在能看見你了
I can see you now.
天啊，你穿的那是件什麼襯衫？
Oh God, what is that shirt you're wearing?
你是從園丁那裏借的嗎？
Have you borrowed it from the gardenkeeper?
事實上，他的和我的襯衫尺寸是一樣的，所以很適合我
Actually, his and mine shirt size is the same. So it fit me!
順便說一下，他的妻子穿XL看起來也是這樣，會適合你
By the way, his wife wears XL. Looks like that too, will fit you!
要是你有什麼是XL號的就好了，不是嗎？
If only you had something XL, no?
寶貝，我有我的心
Baby, I have my heart.
我的心是如此的寬廣
My heart is so big.
好吧，你應該知道，我一直在不丹尋找WiFi信號
OK, you should know, that I haven't been looking for
來聽你這些廢話
wi-fi all over Bhutan, to listen to all these ridicules.
是啊，好像是我要你去不丹似的
Yeah, as if I asked to go to Bhutan!
學習冥想，谘詢項目隻是一個借口
Meditation is being learnt, with Consultancy Project only as an excuse.
如果你想學冥想，你完全可以……
If it's meditation that you wanted to learn, you could've done that
每天早上醒來看電視上的《拉姆德夫巴巴》
just by waking up in the mornings to watch 'Ramdev baba' on the T.V.
對，我就喜歡看那些毛茸茸的老男人在早上6點汗流浹背
Yeah, because I just love old, hairy men sweating at 6 in the morning!
你以為我為什麼要和你上床，寶貝？
Why do you think I sleep with you, baby?
寶貝，我認為你和我上床是因為
Baby, I thought you sleep with me, because not
你在做慈善，不是嗎？
a lot of men, believe in doing charity, no?
你想讓我開始數做慈善的數量嗎？
Oh, you want me to start counting down on the charity cases?
我們是不是應該數數你的約會史?-不不不不..
Should we start listing your dating history, now? -No, no, no, no...
什麼時候我的真愛，撕開雲彩..
When is my true love, by tearing through clouds...
降落在這個我們稱之為印度的土地上
Landing on the grounds of this country, we call India!
四點鍾
Four O'clock!
四點整
Sharp!
你會來接我的，對吧？
You're coming to get me, right?
好的，我8點有個會議，我有很重要的事情要告訴你
Ok, I've a meeting at 8 and I've something very important to tell you.
哦! 我也有很重要的事要告訴你
Oh! Even I've something very important to tell you.
好吧，我先說，求求你，求求你，讓我先說
OK, I'll go first. Please. Please. Let me go first!
好吧，去吧，好像我還有得選似的
OK, go. As if I have a choice.
說吧
Blurt out!
是這樣的……
Actually...
納文，我懷孕了
Naveen, I'm pregnant.
非常好
Very nice!
是誰的孩子？
Who's child is it?
我不知道..
I don't know...
誰都有可能
It could be anyone's.
可能是你的
It could be yours.
可能是拉哈夫的，也可能是瓦伊巴夫的
It could be Raghav's. It could be Vaibhav's.
哦，甚至可能是那個修道士的
Oh, it could even be the monastery monk's.
你有什麼重要的話要說，還是你隻是在浪費我流量
Do you have anything important to say or are you just eating into my internet pack?
不不不我確實有重要的事情要說
No. No. No. I do have something important to say.
但是我想要你一個驚喜
But I'd thought, that I'd keep it a surprise.
我應該告訴你嗎？
Should I tell you?
什麼? 你買了手銬？
What? You bought handcuffs?
是的，但除此之外..
Yeah, but apart from that...
是這樣的
So!
有個人，他要離開他的女朋友去巴西
There's this guy, who's leaving his girlfriend and moving to Brazil.
這個女孩，決定開始找工作
This girl, decides to start looking for a job.
在巴西
In Brazil.
還有，你猜怎麼著？
And, guess what?
她發現自己進入了最後的候選名單
She finds herself in the final shortlist.
史瑞雅! 等等
Shreya! Wait!
隻差一次電話麵試了，在那之後……
...last telephonic interview is left, but after that...
史瑞雅，等等
Shreya, wait.
- 她就跟你一起在裏約生活了!-等等等等
...going to live with you in Rio, bitch! - Wait. Wait. Wait.
等等，史瑞雅
Wait Shreya...
這正是我想告訴你的消息
This is exactly what I wanted to give you news about.
告訴我
Tell me.
呃..
Uh...
你在幹什麼..
What are you doing...
我正要洗呢
I was just about to wash them up
你還要幹多少活
How much will you work, after all!
洗衣機壞了，傭人也冇來..
Anyway, the machine isn't workiing and the maid hasn't come...
冇用多長時間……
It hardly takes time...
洗衣服……
I washed them...
怎麼回事? 你今天突然..
What's the deal? Suddenly today...
不是突然吧
It isn't really "suddenly"!
我前天做了雞肉
I'd cooked chicken, day before!
昨晚，我切的菜
And last night, I'd chopped the vegetables.
在一個家庭中，如果兩個人一起做事，就冇那麼纍了
In a household, if 2 people work in unison, it becomes easy.
現在有了各種各樣的機器……
These days, these machines have come up...
否則..
Otherwise...
我們的父輩以前都是用手做的
Our dads used to do it all, by hands.
你怎麼不去..
Why don't you go...
去祈禱吧，等我做完這裏的事，我就去泡茶
Go do your prayers. I'll come, make tea, once I'm done here.
你有什麼事要跟我說的嗎？
Do you have something, to tell me?
冇有啊
No!
你為什麼這麼想？
Why would you think so?
給我
Give me.
納文... 給我打電話..
Naveen... had called...
尤吉和納文已經辭職了
Yogi and Naveen have quit their jobs...
準備開始創業
They're going to begin their own start-up...
他們問了我……要不要一起
They were asking me... as well
你下樓去吧，我來搞定
You go on downstairs. I'll get done here.
你剛才說什麼？
So what were you saying?
我剛才說什麼來著..
What was I saying...
哦對……
No...
納文和其他人問了我
Naveen and the guys were asking me as well...
要不要辭掉工作，加入他們的公司做CTO
To quit my job and join them as the C.T.O.
但是現在..
But now...
這... 你什麼時候買的？
This... When did you buy this?
這是舊的
This is an old one!
從我父母那來的
Had gotten it from my parents'.
不... ... 我是說... ... 這顔色很適合你... ... 很好看
No... I was saying... These colors suit you... They come out very well!
那你怎麼說？
So what did you say?
我說，我會考慮的... 現在這事情..
I said, I'll think about it... Now things like...
不能一下子就決定了
...these can't just be decided in the moment.
所以我也想和你談談這個
So I wanted to talk to you as well, about this.
這對你的職業發展有益嗎
Will you be benefited, in your career?
如果初創企業發展壯大，那麼是有好處的
If the start-up goes big, then there's a benefit...
否則，這就隻是在冒險
Otherwise, it's just a risk!
工作會很有趣
Well, the work will be a lot of fun...
一定會很有趣的，但是薪水..
It'll be interesting but the salary...
我認為你應該去
I think you should do it.
什麼？
What?
你搞錯了
You're not doing it right...
給我
Give it to me!
不是……
No...
你剛才說什麼？
What were you saying?
我認為，你應該去創業
I think, you should do it.
哈？
No...
真的冇問題嗎？
You don't have any problem?
我是想說……
I was trying to say, that once...
如果我辭職了，我們買房子的計劃就要推遲了
...I quit my job, our plan to buy a house will be delayed.
為什麼要急著買房子呢？
So, what's the hurry in buying a house?
不管怎麼說，現在這房子也不錯
Anyway, this is such a nice house.
這麼大的陽臺
There's such a big terrace!
而且你成長的機會，也會更多
And then the chances of your growth, are also so much more.
我連自助餐都冇有
I won't even get an L.T.A.
我們也不得不取消毛裏求斯之旅
We'll have to drop our Mauritius trip, as well.
我們還是去馬哈巴萊斯赫瓦爾吧
We'll go to Mahabaleshwar, instead.
沙利尼的丈夫有一個渡假村在那
Shalini's husband owns a resort there.
但薪水問題仍然是個問題
But the salary issue will still persist.
我們的儲蓄足夠了
Our savings are good enough.
不管怎樣，我來孟買已經5個月了
Anyway, it's been 5 months since I've come to Mumbai.
我在想..
I'm thinking...
要出去找份工作
...of getting a good job for myself.
這些是怎麼掛的? 用夾子嗎？
How do you hang these? By clips?
我還以為你不會同意呢
I thought, you wouldn't agree to this.
我甚至還準備了流程圖，用來說服你
I even had my flowcharts ready, so that I could convince you!
我從星期一開始就一直在想這個問題
I've only been thinking about this, since Monday.
所有的努力都白費了
All the effort, went waste!
別擔心
Don't worry.
你的努力不會白費
None of your effort will go waste.
不管怎樣..
Anyway...
你還得和你爸爸談談..
You'll have to talk to your dad about this...
你不會不問他就辭職吧？
You wouldn't quit your job, without asking him, would you?
拜托你做事靠譜一些好不好
I was asking you to do it properly!
現在我又得洗衣服了，全都要重洗
Now I'll have to wash, all the clothes again!
傭人今天都冇來
Even the maid's not come today!
撤下所有的講座然後換成色情視頻
...got down all the lectures, and uploaded youporn videos, instead.
這小夥子贏了 IBM 代碼競賽兩次以上..
Our guy's won the IBM code competition, twice over...
還是連續的
...in a row.
據說他收到了埃裏克 · 施密特的祝賀信
Legend says that he got a congratulatory mail from Eric Schmidt, himself.
但是他冇有隨機的期望，不是嗎？
But he doesn't have random expectations, does he?
他知道除了基本生活津貼他什麼都拿不到對吧？
He knows, he won't get anything more than the basic stipend, right?
放鬆點! 他是自己人
Dude, relax! He's our kid!
我們請他吃幾頓燒烤，他就會答應的
We'll offer him a couple of treats at Barbeque Nation and he'll say yes!
我告訴他，這是一個環境科學講座，狗娘養的..
I told him, it's an Environment Science lecture motherf**ker...
如果不是代理，我是不是該打你屁股？
If not proxy, should I whoop your arse?
羅漢·奈吉的房間在這邊嗎？
Is Rohan Negi's room this way?
他在等你嗎？
Is he expecting you?
是的
Yes.
跟我來
Follow me!
你去死吧
You go to hell!
我不想再見到你
I don't want to see your face again!
你不滿足於隻有前戲，是嗎？
You aren't satisfied only with foreplay, are you?
你還得有個後續
You have to have this afterplay of melodrama!
她生氣了，因為那是草莓味的
She got mad because it was strawberry.
隻有杏仁或者開心果，而不是冰淇淋
It isn't ice-cream that you'd get almond and pistachio flavours!
叔叔們，有火柴嗎？
Does the uncle party, have matchsticks?
快去食堂，時間到了
Go run to the canteen. It's time!
叔叔，給他一百塊錢
Uncle, give him a 100 bucks.
掏錢
Give it.
跟我來
Follow me!
我不能再往前走了
I can't go beyond this point.
把你的手機、U盤和硬盤等等任何儲存設備都拿出來
Deposit your mobiles, pendrives, hard-disks and any other storage devices.
前麵那扇門
There's a door ahead...
敲門
Knock it.
敲兩下
Twice!
然後等著
And then wait.
你們抽煙嗎？
Do you smoke?
不抽
No.
辣雞
Kids!
什麼事？
Yes?
告訴欽圖，尤吉·拜亞來了，給他一個實習機會
Tell chintu, that 'Yogi bhaiyaa' is here, to give him an internship.
進來吧
Come in.
坐
Sit.
他正在忙..
He's in the middle of something...
給他75
Give him 75.
分鍾？
Minutes?
爆頭數
Headshots!
盡管我是班長，但我從6年級到12年級的成績穩步提高..
Despite being the class monitor, my performance from class 6 to class 12 steadily increased...
由72.3% 增加至87.8%
From 72.3% to 87.8%
這錶明..
This goes to show...
我有責任..
I'm responsible...
堅持不懈
...persistent...
... 專註，積極，超越..
...dedicated, motivated, over...
被低估……
Under-rated dude!
有責任心，堅持不懈，積極主動，敬業樂業
Responsible, persistent, motivated, dedicated, under...
嗨，史瑞雅
Hi Shreya!
嗨，曼達爾
Hi Mandal!
嗨..
Hi...
對不起，我不是有意打擾你幻想幻燈片的
Sorry, I didn't mean to disturb your paranormal powerpoint fantasy.
我會偷偷霤進納文的房間然後鎖上門，這樣你就不能進來了
I'll just sneak into Naveen's room and lock the door, so you can't come in!
不不不
No. No. No.
事實上，我是在等你
Actually, I was waiting for you!
納文告訴我你會來
Naveen'd told me that you're going to come.
穿著那件運動夾克和毛巾？
In that blazer and towel?
你不是連環殺手曼達爾吧？
You aren't a serial killer Mandal, are you?
隻有外錶能殺人
Only, if looks could kill!
請坐
Please have a seat!
事實上，如果我感到緊張，我要去洗個澡
Actually, if I get tensed, I need to have a bath!
好點了嗎？
Better?
恭喜你，曼達爾
Congratulations Mandal.
你已經到了令人毛骨悚然的新境界
You've reached a new level of creepy!
那麼……
Soo...
納文辭職去..
Naveen's quit his job to...
我知道，他什麼都告訴我了
Yeah, I know. He's told me everything.
我也想..
And I too, want to...
所有的一切
Everything!
那麼……
Soo...
那又怎樣？
So?
史瑞雅，我們是朋友，對吧？
Shreya. We're friends, aren't we?
在 facebook 上還是在現實生活中？
Facebook-wise or in real life?
別鬨
Joke!
你還記得嗎？
Do you remember?
上個月，某個清晨..
Last month, early morning...
你想複印你的 PAN 卡
You wanted a Xerox of your PAN card.
納文正在睡覺
Naveen was sleeping.
所以你找我幫忙
So you asked me for help.
我上班要遲到了..
I was getting late for work...
我身上冇帶零錢
I didn't have any change on me...
但我還是去把複印機弄好了
I still went and got the Xerox done.
聽著，我有一個哲學理論
Look, I've this one philosophy...
朋友應該互相幫助
Friends should always help each other!
不不不不不
No. No. No. No. No.
等一下
One second.
你想讓我說服納文帶你創業？
You want me to convince Naveen to hire you?
不行
No.
對不起
Sorry.
想都不要想
Not gonna happen.
不管怎樣，我不能說服他，相反，他最終會說服我
Anyway, I can't convince him. Instead, he'll end up convincing me!
史瑞雅... 相信我
Shreya... Trust me!
他絕對不能說服你
He can never convince you!
男人永遠都不能說服給了他……
A man can never convince a woman, who gives him...
... 愛的女人
...Love!
如果..
And if...
他不動搖的話……
He doesn't budge...
你知道..
You know...
用你的方法……
Use your methods!
什麼方法？
What methods?
性交
Intercourse
什麼？
What?
曼達爾，你瘋了嗎？
Mandal, have you gone nuts?
那個隻要1塊錢的複印機..
Just for a 1 buck Xerox...
實際上是兩塊錢，要複印兩麵呢
It's actually 2 bucks. One for each side!
我的價值遠不止這些
I'm worth much more than that!
好嗎? 對不起
OK? I'm sorry.
我可以幫你做其他的事情，但是這件事，我做不到! 對不起
I would've helped you with anything else, but with this, I can't! Sorry.
納文需要我的幫助
Naveen needs my help!
尤吉一直從中作梗不讓我加入
Yogi keeps winding him up against me!
我真的很想成為其中的一員
I really want to be a part of this!
我知道，我一定會後悔的
I know, I'm gonna regret this.
好吧
OK.
Alright.
我要確認一件事
Tell me one thing.
你會在什麼時候……
When do...
叫水管工？
You call for a plumber?
那不是我..
That wasn't me...
納文以為我弄壞了他的噴霧然後..
Naveen thinks that I broke his jet spray and then...
不，我是說假設
No. I mean hypothetically.
我是說..
I mean...
什麼時候會有人叫水管工？
When would anyone, call for a plumber?
水龍頭壞了，就叫水管工來
One calls for the plumber when a tap's broken.
對，如果水龍頭冇壞呢？
Right. And what if a tap isn't broken?
那為什麼要叫水管工？
Then why call the plumber?
冇錯
Exactly!
你看
Look.
在這種情況下..
In this situation...
你是水管工，但納文的公司並冇有壞掉的水龍頭
You're the plumber and Naveen's start-up doesn't have any broken tap.
無論你在生活中所做的貢獻有多麼偉大
Irrespective of, however great, the work you're doing in life is...
除非你的加入能解決他們的問題..
Unless, your inclusion doesn't solve any of their problems...
否則他們就不會需要你
They don't need you!
你要弄清楚他們需要什麼
See... You need to figure out what they need.
你還需要一條更大的毛巾
You also need a bigger towel, dude!
別走
No. No.
不要回避
Don't shy away!
我穿著內褲呢
I'm wearing my underwear!
對不起
Sorry.
冇穿
Not wearing any!
幹你娘
F**K!
去你丫的
尤吉
Yogi!
還有..
And...
你一定是納文
You must be Naveen.
你好呀欽圖，我上次在穿線儀式上見過你
How are you 'chintu'? I saw you at the threading ceremony, last.
不是欽圖
Not 'chintu'.
地下城主
Dungeon Master.
在地下城和主人之間有一個下劃線
There's an underscore between Dungeon and Master.
所以..
So...
你們想讓我為你們公司工作
You guys want me to work for your company.
你跟他講
You tell him.
我們有興趣討論一下..
We were interested in discussing the possibilities...
我研究了你的想法
I looked into your idea.
其實挺有意思的
It's... quite interesting actually.
研究過了嗎？
Looked into?
但是，到目前為止，我還冇有給你發過郵件
But, I haven't sent you any mail, as yet!
但是你已經給 NASSCOM 發過了，不是嗎？
But you'd mailed NASSCOM, hadn't you?
你看..
You see...
郵件隱私是個神話，我的朋友
Privacy on mail is a myth my friend!
所以... 如果我加入你們..
So... If I join you guys...
我有什麼好處
How do I benefit?
我能得到什麼？
What do I get?
機會
Opportunity!
當然，一開始也會有一筆津貼
Of course, there'll also be a stipend initially.
大約... 7仟塊
About... 7K.
8... 8仟
8... 8K. Yeah.
隨著我們公司的發展，你們的工資也會增加
And as we grow, your monetory compensation will obviously increase...
你知道國際反恐精英大賽的獎金是多少嗎？
Do you know what's the prize money for the Internation Counter Strike competition?
多少錢？
How much?
475,000...
美元
Dollars.
4... 4乘以6等於24..
4... 4 times 6 is 24...
你贏了？
And you won that?
兩次
Twice!
4... 4乘2等於8... 8乘6等於48..
4... 4 times 2 is 8... 8 times 6 is 48...
所以理論上來說... 我可以雇傭你們
So theoritically... I can hire you guys.
而不是你雇傭我
But not the other way round.
我要30% 的股權
I want 30% equity...
還有... 否決産品設計
And... veto on product design.
Dungeon_master@hotmail.com
不要忘記下劃線
Don't forget the underscore.
星期一之前給我發郵件
Mail me by Monday.
或者把它保存在你的草稿中
Or just save it in your drafts.
我會看的
I'll read it.
我想我們需要傑圖
I think we need Jeetu.
你認為我們需要傑圖嗎？
Do you think we need Jeetu?
我們需要傑圖
We need Jeetu.
我們必須先更改所有賬戶的密碼
We'll have to first change the passwords for all our accounts.
怎麼了，創業者？
What's up, start-up founder?
談完這筆交易後，你們的電池看起來冇電了
Your battery looks dead after listeninig to the deal.
怎麼了，企業家叔叔？
What's up, entrepreneur uncle?
給我們也分一些股份吧
Pass on some stake to us as well!
聽著，傑圖，冇有別的出路了，你必須加入進來
Listen up Jeetu. There's no other way out. You have to join in.
我不能參加了
I can't join in.
對不起
Sorry.
我告訴過你
I told you!
你永遠不能說服一個跟你上床的女人
You can never convince a woman who gives you sex!
不
Noo!
桑亞已經同意了
Suamya has agreed.
所以呢？
SO?
哦
Ohh!
什麼？
What?
你有冇有試著和他談談？
Did you try talking to him?
這就是我從一歲半開始一直想做的事情
That's all I've been able to do since I was 1.5 years old. TRY to talk!
和誰？
With whom?
你冇看過《烏丹》嗎？
Haven't you watched 'Udaan'?
哦
Ohhhh!
你爸爸？
Your dad?
他酗酒？
He's alcoholic?
他不是酒鬼..
He's not alcoholic...
你為什麼害怕你爸爸? 你還是個孩子嗎？
Why are you scared of your dad? Are you still a kid?
納文，我的存摺都在他那裏
Naveen. Even my passbook is with him.
如果下個月一號我的工資還冇有到賬
If my salary doesn't get credited on the 1st of the next month...
我就得用命來頂
My life will get debited.
你們先開始吧
You guys, atleast, start.
我會試著每天下班後投入幾個小時的工作
I'll see. I'll try putting in a couple of hours of work, everyday after my job.
”你們先做””我等等看”你瘋了嗎？
"You guys start", "I'll see". Are you mad?
這樣的話，即使是測試版6個月之內也做不好
This way, even the Beta version won't be ready in 6 months.
還有很多事情要做
There's so much to do.
不好意思
Excuse me!
這不是印度曆史上最酷的公司嗎？
Aren't you the guys launching the coolest company of Indian history?
嘿! 創業的太太來了-嘿
Hey! The start-up wags are here. -Hey!
那些拜金主義者甚至比錢還早到這裏
The gold-diggers are here even before the money.
聽著，你需要一個更好的首席執行官
Listen, you need to get a better CEO, though!
不知道是不是最酷的，但肯定是最短命的
Don't know about the coolest, but could be most short-lived for sure!
不要在這樣的好日子裏說喪氣話，傑圖
Don't say such bad things on a good day like this, Jeetu.
這是給你的
This is for you'll.
怎麼了，傑圖？
So what's up, Jeetu?
你在這兒幹什麼？
What are you doing here?
我是來麵試的
I've come here for the interview!
曼達爾，那隻是個玩笑，不會有麵試的
Mandal, that was only a joke. There's no interview happening.
我知道，我知道
I know. I know.
我懂笑話
I know jokes.
我上了一個月的即興喜劇課
I've taken improv. comedy classes for a month.
這有人嗎?-有
Is this taken? -Yes.
好的
OK!
你還不明白嗎，混蛋？
Don't you get it, motherf**ker?
我們的電池冇電了
Anyway our battery's down...
這是我們的事，曼達爾
This is our shit, Madal!
我們不需要你
We don't need you.
相信我
Trust me.
你需要我
You need me!
事實上冇有我..
Infact without me...
你冇有公司
You don't have a company!
好吧，去拿把椅子來
OK, go get a chair.
我們現在麵試你
We'll interview you right away!
聽他把話說完，就一次
Just hear him out na, once.
告訴我
Tell me.
我們為什麼要雇傭你？
Why should we hire you?
作為一個工商管理碩士
You know, as an MBA...
我一直對我的角色與責任很清楚
I've always had a clarity about my R&Rs.
我的一個主要關鍵領域出了問題..
One of my KRA has been problem...
我們不需要市場經理，我們需要一個程序員..
We don't need a marketing manager. We need a coder...
謝謝你的申請，麵試結束
Thanks for applying. You interview's over.
不不不等一下
No. No. No. One second.
我可以解決你的問題
I can solve your problem.
我可以給你一些你需要的東西
I can give you something, which you need.
我可以給你傑圖
I can give you Jeetu!
怎麼做？
How?
現階段，你不會得到任何投資..
Till the time, you'll don't get an investment...
由我來付傑圖的工資
I'll pay for Jeetu's salary.
一部分是我的工資，另一部分是我的積蓄
A part of it through my salary and a part through my savings.
但我保證，傑圖現在的工資是多少，我就給他多少
But I'll ensure that, Jeetu keeps getting as much as he gets from his company.
曼達爾你為什麼要為我們做這些事？
Mandal. Why would you do these things for us?
不是為你們
Not for you guys...
我是為了我自己
I'll do it for myself!
你們是我最好的朋友
You guys are the best friends I've ever had.
我知道除了納文
I know, apart from Naveen...
我們並冇有很多交流的機會
We've not interacted as much...
但是我一直認為，我們四個是一個非常好的團隊
But I've always thought, that the four of us are a very good team.
當我看《人隻活一次》的時候
You know when I'd seen 'Zindagi Milegi Na Dobara'
我決定..
I'd decided that...
我們四個也是，就像電影主角一樣……
The four of us too, just like them...
開創一番事業
Would go on a trip.
但是主角隻有3個人
But ZNMD had only 3 guys.
好吧，那麼... 就三個主角
OK. Then... like 'Dil Chahta Hai'.
再說一次，隻有三個人，曼達爾
Again, only 3 guys, Mandal.
搖滾樂隊肯定有4個人
'Rock On' definitely had 4 guys.
第四個得了癌癥死了，隻剩下三個
The 4th one, gets cancer and dies. Only 3 remain.
重點是如果我加入你們的初創公司
The point is, if I join your start-up...
這樣傑圖就可以全職和我們一起工作了
Then Jeetu can work full-time with us.
不是所有的MBA都那麼糟糕
All MBAs... are not that bad.
那麼……
Soo...
有人要說什麼嗎，還是我們就這樣坐一個小時？
Is somebody going to say something, or are we sitting just like this for the next hour?
別擔心，夥計們
Don't worry, guys.
不會那麼糟的
It won't be that bad.
後街男孩... 歐耶
Backstreet Boys... Alright!
幹杯
Cheers!
我們有四個人啦
And then there were four!
幹杯! 幹杯! 幹杯
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
終於，他讓自己變得有用了
Finally, he's made himself useful!
好了，傑圖回來了
So, Jeetu's back!
最重要的一點 -這個消息不能從這裏傳出去
Important point - This news doesn't get out of here!
如果爸爸知道了... - 別再說什麼”爸爸爸爸”了
If dad gets to know... - Stop going "Dad. Dad."
一旦我們成為價值百萬美元的公司，你爸爸也會冷靜下來的
Once we're a million dollar company, even your dad will chill out!
此外，我還做了一些研究，為我們的公司想了幾個名字
And also, I've done some research and thought of a few names for our compnay.
我想，我們公司的名字裏應該有‘ le’
I think, our compnay name should have 'le' in it!
就像Google，Apple，Oracle
Like Google had 'gle', Apple has 'ple', Oracle has 'cle'
你在胡說些什麼? 你又開始用你那愚蠢的營銷邏輯了
What non-sense are you talking? You've started with your stupid marketing logics again!
請不要往我身上扔薯條，我是市場部經理
Please don't throw fries on me. I'm the marketing manager!
對不起
Oops! Sorry.
餵！為什麼要扔我
Careful! Why are you throwing it on me?
這就是你的百萬美元團隊？
So, this is your million dollar team?
恭喜
Congrats